{
  "subject": "Mathematics",
  "year": 2020,
  "quiz": [
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Find the area of a circle whose diameter is 14cm. (π = 22/7)",
      "options": {
        "A": "140cm²",
        "B": "144cm²",
        "C": "154cm²",
        "D": "164cm²",
        "E": "540cm²"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "If a number multiplies itself to give 289, what is the number?",
      "options": {
        "A": "11",
        "B": "12",
        "C": "13",
        "D": "15",
        "E": "17"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "If an orange costs Np, how much will q oranges cost?",
      "options": {
        "A": "N(p q)",
        "B": "N()",
        "C": "N(p + 1)",
        "D": "N(p + q)",
        "E": "N(pq)"
      },
      "correct": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "Simplify (2³ × 5²) + 5.",
      "options": {
        "A": "10",
        "B": "20",
        "C": "40",
        "D": "100",
        "E": "200"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "What is the value of y in the diagram below?",
      "options": {
        "A": "5cm",
        "B": "8cm",
        "C": "12cm",
        "D": "18cm",
        "E": "20cm"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "The area of a rectangle is 60cm². Find the length of the rectangle, if its breadth is 5cm.",
      "options": {
        "A": "65cm",
        "B": "25cm",
        "C": "15cm",
        "D": "13cm",
        "E": "12cm"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "Bello had N550.00 and spent N280.00 on drugs. How much does he have left?",
      "options": {
        "A": "N150.00",
        "B": "N170.00",
        "C": "N230.00",
        "D": "N270.00",
        "E": "N330.00"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "If 1 cm on a map represents 15m, what does 3.5cm represent?",
      "options": {
        "A": "4.3m",
        "B": "11.5m",
        "C": "18.5m",
        "D": "23.3m",
        "E": "52.5m"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "Find the value of x−3, if 14 + x = 3.",
      "options": {
        "A": "28",
        "B": "21",
        "C": "7",
        "D": "-14",
        "E": "3"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "The volume of a cube is 64cm³. Find the length of the cube.",
      "options": {
        "A": "3cm",
        "B": "4cm",
        "C": "5cm",
        "D": "6cm",
        "E": "7cm"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "Calculate the circumference of a circle of radius 3.5cm. (π = 22/7)",
      "options": {
        "A": "77cm",
        "B": "75cm",
        "C": "44cm",
        "D": "22cm",
        "E": "18cm"
      },
      "correct": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "If 2x − 18 = 0, find the value of x.",
      "options": {
        "A": "0",
        "B": "1",
        "C": "2",
        "D": "8",
        "E": "9"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "Solve for y, if 13 = ½ + y.",
      "options": {
        "A": "6",
        "B": "10",
        "C": "15",
        "D": "30",
        "E": "32"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Find the average of the following set of numbers: 1, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11.",
      "options": {
        "A": "5",
        "B": "6",
        "C": "7",
        "D": "8",
        "E": "9"
      },
      "correct": "B"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Find the volume of a cylinder of radius 2cm and height 14cm. (π = 22/7)",
      "options": {
        "A": "120cm³",
        "B": "136cm³",
        "C": "142cm³",
        "D": "151cm³",
        "E": "176cm³"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "Find the mode of the set of numbers: 4, 3, 7, 5, 3, 6, 7, 3.",
      "options": {
        "A": "7",
        "B": "6",
        "C": "5",
        "D": "4",
        "E": "3"
      },
      "correct": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "If the area of a rectangle is 24cm² and the length is 8cm, find the breadth.",
      "options": {
        "A": "16cm",
        "B": "12cm",
        "C": "10cm",
        "D": "6cm",
        "E": "3cm"
      },
      "correct": "D"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "Find the value of x in the diagram below.",
      "options": {
        "A": "115°",
        "B": "80°",
        "C": "70°",
        "D": "65°",
        "E": "20°"
      },
      "correct": "C"
    }
  ]
}
